Guide to the Missionary Ephemera Collection
Yale University Divinity School Library
Missionary Ephemera Collection
1820-1992
RG 221
Yale University Divinity School Library
32
(52 boxes + 21 portfolios)
This collection includes a wide range of missionary ephemera, including artifacts, calendars, cards, children's materials, games, maps, posters, stamps, photographs, and lantern slides.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The items were acquired by donation and purchase.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
During the height of the missionary movement of the late 19th and early 20th centuries, tens of thousands of missionaries went abroad, seeking to spread their Christian beliefs and bringing with them their devotion to Western civilization. This collection contains materials that were used to convey the missionaries' message to the people with whom they were working, including posters, broadsides, and tracts. It also includes materials used to encourage the home public to understand and support the missionary enterprise, including postcards, publications, calendars, collection boxes, artifacts, cards, and games.
Scope and Contents
This finding aid represents an inventory of "missionary ephemera" held by the Yale Divinity Library. Images of some of the materials in the collection are featured in an online exhibit: Spreading the Word: A Selection of Missionary Posters, Games, and Ephemera from the Day Missions Collection. The descriptions of materials will be refined as possible in the future and additional images made available.
More than 100 Chinese posters in this collection have been digitized and described as part of the Chinese Christian Posters project at Boston University. See http://ccposters.com/library/yale-divinity-library/.
Arrangement
I. Artifacts
II. Calendars
III. Cards
IV. Children's Materials
V. Diplomas, Certificates, Receipts
VI. Games
VII. Maps
VIII. Obituary Cards, Biographical Documentation
IX. Posters, Illustrations, Banners
X. Stamps, Stationery
XI. Miscellaneous Items
XII. Photographs
XIII. Lantern Slides and Glass Negatives
Missions
- Artifacts, Series I
  - Collection box with art by Dennis Cusick, 1821 (Box OV12)
    Scope and Contents
    Dennis Cusick (c. 1800–1824) was a Tuscarora painter from New York and a founder of the Iroquois Realist Style of painting. There are three images on the box, including a depiction of a Seneca schoolhouse. The box was presented to the United Foreign Missionary Society of New York by James Young.
  - Missionary collection banks, no date (Box OV1, Folder 1)
    Seven banks including: Church Missionary Society Medical Mission Auxiliary Collection Bank; J.M.A. Methodist Missionary Society; London Missionary Society; The C.S.S.M. – The Missionary Helpers' Union; South American Missionary Society, "A Light That Shineth In A Dark Place"; Evangelical and Interdenominational Zambesi Mission; Mission to Mediterranean Garrisons founded by Mrs. Todd Osborne
  - Buttons, badges, pendants, and pins, early 1900s (Box OV1, Folder 2)
    WMS 30th Anniversary Cross Pin 1892-1922 Presbyterian Church Board of Foreign Missions Pin Women's Missionary Fellowship Pin Christian Missionary Alliance Pin World Pontifical Missionary Pin 'Les Saints Martyrs Canadiens' Pendant African Missionary Lapel Button Missionary Day Pinback 1919 Methodist Centenary Movement Mission Pin 1921 50th Anniversary Woman's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society (WABFMS) Pin 1916 Missionary Enlisted Service Pinback Political Button 1939 Missionary Exhibition Badge – Australian Board of Missions 1913 Australia Pacific Missionary Fair pin back badge Woman's Foreign Missionary Society Pinback Button Australian Inland Mission Far North Health Scheme Badge Laymen's Missionary Convention Badge, 1910 1911 Missionary Exposition Button
  - Coins, medallions, medals, and tokens, late 1800s (Box OV1, Folder 3)
    Rosebud Missionary Society Certificate (1921) and 2 Coins 1895 Centenary of the London Missionary Society Medal Baptist Missionary Society Centenary 1792-1892 Medallion 1844 Commemorative Medal John Williams Missionary Ship Bronze Medal Unione Missionarie Francescana Medal, Saint John Gabirel Perboyre, Chinese Martyr Old Spanish Missionary Medallion Martyr St. Pedro Calungsod Holy Medal 19th Century Finnish Evangelical Mission Token from China
  - Rosary and two rosary cards, no date (Box OV1, Folder 4)
  - Large medallions, 1979 (Box OV1, Folder 5)
    India, Saint John of Brito, Jesuit Missionary, Martyr India, Saint John of Brito, Jesuit Missionary, Martyr, 1979
- Calendars, Series II
  - Missionarissen van Scheut calendar, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Franciscanes Missionnaires de Marie calendar, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kansas Woman's Christian Missionary Society calendar, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Augustinian Missionary Calendar, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 3 Oeuvre Pontificale de La Sainte-Enfance calendars, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    One calendar is from 1939 and two are from 1940.
  - "Primavera Missionaria" calendar, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lott Carey Baptist Foreign Mission Convention calendar, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Two Aidez Les Missions de Scheut calendars, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes their covers and a letter from Cardinal Joseph E. Van Roey.
  - Giornata Missionaria Mondiale Calendar, the Pontificie Opere Missionarie, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Calendario Missionario, Missione Delle Piccole Figlie Di S. Giuseppe – Verona, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Calendrier, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1963 Calendario: francescano dei piccolo missionary cappuccino toscani (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cards, Series III
  - Complete trading card set on Ramon Luli, no date (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 9 Cards issued by the Missionaries of the Sacred Heart, no date (Box 2, Folder 2)
    9 Cards issued by the Missionaries of the Sacred Heart for contributions to support missionary activities.
  - Complete set of 18 cards issued by the Catholic Church to support Father Damien's work, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Separated Materials
    Complete set of 18 cards issued by the Catholic Church in 1890 for donations of 10 centimes to support the missionary work begun by Father Damien.
  - 12 Berean Lesson Pictures published by The Methodist Book Concern, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 12 Bible leaflets issued by the Scripture Gift Mission, no date (Box 2, Folder 5)
    These leaflets were issued in the United Kingdom for donations to support missionary activities abroad.
  - 30 cards about the Boxer Rebellion by Ogden Cigarettes, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Set of 10 chromo cards by Belgian company Superchocolat Jacques, no date (Box 2, Folder 7)
    The subject of these cards is missionary work in the Belgian Congo.
  - Liebig card set entitled, "The Holy Year and its Origins", 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Complete set of Liebig trade cards entitled, "The History of Cribs", 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    These cards relate to the Nativity in different continents.
  - Complete set of Belgian Liebig trade cards entitled, "Ecumenical Councils", 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - German Card reading "White Man! Please buy me!" on the front, with a description of interactions between the slave markets and Catholic Missionaries in Africa, no date (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Two Stereoview Cards, one of Egypt, one of Guam, no date (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 11-piece set of cards of the Congo by N. Vandenhoudt Scheut, no date (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 12 "Chocolat d'Aiguebelle" trading cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 83 cards depicting children from various countries, no date (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 6 San Giovanni Bosco cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 28 Asian-language Missionary Cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 6 Missionary Cards of unidentified origin, no date (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 12 English-language Missionary Cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 18 German-language Missionary Cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 6 Spanish-language Missionary Cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1 Swahili-language Missionary Card and 1 Zulu-language Missionary Card, no date (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1 Slovenian Missionary Card, no date (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 166 Italian Missionary Cards, no date (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 25 cards printed by Providence Lithograph Co. with English on the front and Arabic on the back., no date (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 155 French Missionary Cards, no date (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 335 Dutch-language Missionary Cards, no date (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 157 Dutch-language Missionary Cards, no date (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Set of 24 Spanish chromo cards entitled "The Plagues of Mankind", no date (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous illustrated cards and leaflets, mostly from Catholic mission agencies, no date (Box 32)
- Children's Materials, Series IV
  - "A Missionary Story" by Charlotte Murray, no date (Box OV1, Folder 6)
  - "Latin America: A Missionary Color Book for Children" by Theodore W. Engstrom and Paul Hubartt, 1950 (Box OV1, Folder 7)
  - "Japan: A Missionary Color Book for Children" by Theodore W. Engstrom and Paul Hubartt, 1948 (Box OV1, Folder 8)
  - 4 children's books in comic book format on the life of Don Bosco, 1956 (Box OV1, Folder 9)
  - German Mission Booklets for Children, 1932-1936 (Box OV1, Folder 10)
  - Mission Book in German from Luxemburg for Children, no date (Box OV1, Folder 11)
  - Collection of Japanese games for children, no date (Box OV1, Folder 12)
    This collection includes a picture map of Japan for children to color, the book "Taro: A Little Boy of Japan" by Constance Burgess and Andrew Burgess, cut-out paper figures, the book "Japan: A Missionary Color Book for Children" by Theodore W. Engstrom and Paul Hubartt, and the book "Children of Japan: Selected from the around the world picture sets" by Janet Smalley and Nina Millen.
- Diplomas, Certificates, Receipts, Series V
  - Two 19th Century Salvation Army receipts and one ticket for a lecture, late 1800s (Box OV2, Folder 1)
  - Receipt for money donated to stop the work of Christian Missions, no date (Box OV2, Folder 2)
  - Receipt from the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1856 (Box OV2, Folder 3)
    Receipt from the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions for a ten-cent donation to fund the building of the Missionary Packet, Morning Star. Signed by Treasurer James M. Gordon.
  - Two receipts for donations to the Central Institution "Or Mizion", Yeshiva & Talmud Torah, for the Refugee children saved from the Missionaries., no date (Box OV2, Folder 4)
  - Two diplomas for completion of junior religious studies, written in Italian, 1953 (Box OV2, Folder 5)
  - Italian diploma for Christian education and adopting a child to be baptized at a Mission, 1953 (Box OV2, Folder 6)
  - Certificate of proof of being a Christian by the Missie van Coquilhatstad in the Belgian Congo for a young native girl., no date (Box OV2, Folder 7)
  - Certificate of one share in "The Morning Star", no date (Box OV2, Folder 8)
    "The Morning Star" was a missionary ship that sailed to Micronesia, the Marquesas Islands, Hawaii, Around Cape Horn, and other parts of the South Pacific
  - Proof of membership in a club to support missionary activities. Award is a 'missionary coin.', no date (Box OV2, Folder 9)
  - Church Missionary Society Certificate of Membership in the Young People's Union, 1936 (Box OV2, Folder 10)
  - Italian certificate of baptism by the Associazione Missionaria Bertoni, China, no date (Box OV2, Folder 11)
  - Book of Scripture Examination Awards given to Arthur Long by the Methodist Youth Department, 1956-1958 (Box OV2, Folder 12)
  - 3 Diplomas for Examinations in Missionary Knowledge given to Marjorie Botting, 1925-1927 (Box OV2, Folder 13)
  - 1886 Life Member Certificate for Sarah E. Lee from the Methodist Episcopal Church Juvenile Missionary Society of Degrool Church Auxiliary Missionary Society, June 27, 1886 (Box OV2, Folder 14)
  - Certificate of Baptism, Istituto Missioni Estere-Parma, 1951 (Box OV2, Folder 15)
  - Three membership certificates issued by the Children's Missionary Society of the Lutheran Church to members of the Smith family, 1874 and 1880 (Box OV2, Folder 16)
    Two certificates are dated 1874 and one is dated 1880
  - Methodist reward certificate given to Evelyn Butler for collecting money for missionary work, 1923 (Box OV2, Folder 17)
  - Award in French and Dutch, no date (Box OV2, Folder 18)
  - Award in French, no date (Box OV2, Folder 19)
  - Award in Dutch, no date (Box OV2, Folder 20)
  - Confirmation Certificate for a Reformed church, 1886 (Box OV2, Folder 21)
  - American Missionary Association diploma presented to Jonas Coolidge Biggs, August 30, 1865 (Box OV2, Folder 22)
- Games, Series VI
  - "Missionary Puzzle and 4 Others", including Missionaries and Cannibals, Staggered Colors, Change About, Double Up, and Sorting Out., no date (Box OV3, Folder 1)
    Made in the USA by The Embossing Company, Albany, NY.
  - "Snapshots: A Missionary Card Game" by the Church Missionary Society, Salisbury Square, London, no date (Box OV3, Folder 2)
  - "The Missionary Journeys of St. Paul: A Sunday Pastime Complete with Maps" (Box OV3, Folder 3)
    Victorian Missionary Game
  - Two Italian children's games based on missionary themes, 1930s (Box OV3, Folder 4)
    One issued during the period of Pope Pius XI (1922-1939) showing colonial possessions in Abyssinia. The other is issued by Pro Pontifica Della Santa Infanzia and dated 1939.
  - "Namango of the Ivory Coast: An interest-packed missionary story for the flannelboard", 1960 (Box OV3, Folder 5)
  - Missionary Conquest: One Giant Game of Laughter and Strategy, 1992 (Box OV3, Folder 6)
- Maps, Series VII
  - Supplement No. 6 of the Journal "Missions in China and the Congo" – Map of the Belgian Congo area, no date (Box OV4, Folder 1)
  - Map of Bassin de la Karuzi (Burundi), Publications de L'Institut National pour L'Etude Agronomique Du Congo, no date (Box OV4, Folder 2)
  - Religious Map of Madras showing churches and missions, c. 1820 (Box OV4, Folder 3)
  - Religious Map of Calcutta showing churches and missions, c.1820 (Box OV4, Folder 4)
  - Missionary map of China by the Student Volunteer movement for Foreign Missions, compiled by Harlan P. Beach, 1912 (Box OV4, Folder 5)
  - Map of the location of the three stations of the Mision De Bombay – Surat, Broach, and Rajpipla, no date (Box OV4, Folder 6)
  - Map of French Equatorial Africa showing various Missions and their limits, 1933 (Box OV4, Folder 7)
  - Near-complete set of 19 missionary maps issued once a year by the Journal Les Missions Catholiques, 1893-1913 (Box OV4, Folder 8)
  - Welt-Karte Der Mission, map of the world with images depicting each continent surrounding it, no date (Box OV4, Folder 9)
  - New England map, reproduction of Captain John Smith's map, 1614 (Box OV4, Folder 10)
  - The Western Front, map of France and part of Germany during WWI, no date (Box OV4, Folder 11)
  - Copy of a map of Micronesia, no date (Box OV4, Folder 12)
  - National Geographic map of Illinois, 1931 (Box OV4, Folder 13)
  - Map of Japan for Tourists, published by The Welcome Society of Japan. Includes a small map of the World., 1897 (Box OV4, Folder 14)
  - Plan of World's Columbian Exposition and Handy Map of Chicago, 1893 (Box OV4, Folder 15)
    Compliments of Henry R. Worthington, New York, U.S.A.
  - 2 Maps of Europe and The Near East created by the National Geographic Society, 1929 (Box OV4, Folder 16)
  - Map of Europe showing countries as established by the Peace Conference at Paris, published by The National Geographic Magazine, 1920 (Box OV4, Folder 17)
  - Archaeology of Jerusalem Map of the First Temple, Second Temple, and Byzantine Periods, 1985 (Box OV4, Folder 18)
    Published as part of The Wide Screen Project.
  - Map of the Southeastern United States, compiled and drawn by the National Geographic Society, 1947 (Box OV4, Folder 19)
  - Map of the Islands of the Pacific, no date (Box OV4, Folder 20)
  - Map of The Far East, compiled and drawn by the National Geographic Society, 1952 (Box OV4, Folder 21)
  - Map of Switzerland, created as a specimen page of the New World Loose Leaf Atlas, no date (Box OV4, Folder 22)
    The back contains an Index of Switzerland with the latest census.
  - Booklet with maps of Guiana and South America in it, 1871 (Box OV4, Folder 23)
  - Booklet with maps of Canada, Labrador, Greenland, the West Indies and Central America, and Jamaica, no date (Box OV4, Folder 24)
  - Cloth map with France, Belgium, Holland, and the Pyrenees on the front and France, Spain, and the German-Swiss Frontier on the back, no date (Box OV4, Folder 25)
  - Cloth map entitled, "Revell's Map of St. Paul's Journeys by G.W. Bacon, F.R.G.S.", no date (Box OV4, Folder 26)
  - 2 World Maps, Copyright by Universum-Verlag – München-Solln, April, 1977 (Box OV4, Folder 27)
    The maps have Psalm 89:11-12 written above them and insets all around them. Made by Christian Aid. Two copies of discussion notes are included with the maps.
  - Book entitled "Maps of the World's Nations, Volume II: Africa", January, 1977 (Box OV4, Folder 28)
  - Nouvelle Carte du Congo Belge et de ses Voies de Communication, made by Jas. Hennessy & Co Cognac., no date (Box OV4, Folder 29)
  - Book with maps of Asian countries, no date (Box OV4, Folder 30)
  - Map of Indonesia, particularly the Mentawei Islands off the coast of Sumatra, no date (Box OV7, Folder 1)
  - Map of part of the Island of Sumatra in Indonesia (Box OV7, Folder 2)
  - Map of Nias, an Indonesian Island, no date (Box OV7, Folder 3)
  - Map entitled, "The Anglican Church in the Pacific", prepared for the Australian Board of Missions by H.E.C. Robinson Pty. Ltd., no date (Box OV7, Folder 4)
  - Map entitled "Council of Churches in Indonesia", including a map of Indonesia and statistics about various churches throughout the Islands, 1972 (Box OV7, Folder 5)
  - French map of Madagascar, 1951 (Box OV7, Folder 6)
  - Double-sided Lutheran Mission map of New Guinea, no date (Box OV7, Folder 7)
  - Australian map of New Guinea entitled, "Unevangelized Fields of Mission", no date (Box OV7, Folder 8)
  - Two maps of the "Territory of Papua and New Guinea" with an alphabetical index to the geographical names on the back, 1964 (Box OV7, Folder 9)
  - Map of the territory of Papua and New Guinea with administration and local government organization listed in relation to population distribution, November, 1965 (Box OV7, Folder 10)
    Made by E. Ford Australian School of Pacific Administration
  - Map of the Fiji Islands, no date (Box OV7, Folder 11)
  - Map of the New Hebrides islands without the Torres or parts of the Banks islands, published by the Australian Presbyterian Board of Missions, no date (Box OV7, Folder 12)
  - Belgian map of Southwest Mongolia, 1902 (Box OV7, Folder 13)
  - Two Asian fascicles of the atlas, "Allgemeiner Missions-Atlas nach Originalquellen", published by Gotha: Justus Perthes, 1868 (Box OV7, Folder 14)
  - Two Asian fascicles of the atlas, "Allgemeiner Missions-Atlas nach Originalquellen", published by Gotha: Justus Perthes, 1869 (Box OV7, Folder 15)
  - An American fascicle of the atlas, "Allgemeiner Missions-Atlas nach Originalquellen", published by Gotha: Justus Perthes, 1871 (Box OV7, Folder 16)
  - A Polynesian fascicle of the atlas, "Allgemeiner Missions-Atlas nach Originalquellen", published by Gotha: Justus Perthes, 1870 (Box OV7, Folder 17)
  - Cerographic Missionary Atlas published by Sidney E. Horse & Co., for the New York Observer, 1848 (Box OV7, Folder 18)
  - Map of South Africa showing the location of mission stations and the location of churches and colleges in Cape Town, 1824 (Box OV7, Folder 19)
- Obituary Cards, Biographical Documentation, Series VIII
  - A (by surname of missionary), no date (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - B, no date (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - B, continued, no date (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - B, continued, no date (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - B, continued, no date (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - B, continued, no date (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - B, continued, no date (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - C, no date (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - C, continued, no date (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - C, continued, no date (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - D, no date (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - D, continued, no date (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - D, continued, no date (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - D, continued, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - D, continued, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - E, no date (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - F, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - G, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - G, continued, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - G, continued, no date (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - H, no date (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - H, continued, no date (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - H, continued, no date (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - I, no date (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - J, no date (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - K, no date (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - K, continued, no date (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - L, no date (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - L, continued, no date (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - L, continued, no date (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - M, no date (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - M, continued, no date (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - M, continued, no date (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - M, continued, no date (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - N, no date (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - O, no date (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - P, no date (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - P, continued, no date (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Q, no date (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - R, no date (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - R, continued, no date (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - S, no date (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - S, continued, no date (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - S, continued, no date (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - S, continued, no date (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - S, continued, no date (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - T, no date (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - U, no date (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - V, no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - V, continued, no date (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - V, continued, no date (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - V, continued, no date (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - V, continued, no date (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - W, no date (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - W, continued, no date (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Y, no date (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Z, no date (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous obituaries (Box 14, Folder 1)
    These miscellaneous obituaries include cards without specified names, cards with multiple names, etc.
  - "Hulde aan de Geloofsverkondigers uit de Dekenij Gistel", gives listings of dozens of missionaries from Belgium., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Posters, Illustrations, Banners, Series IX
  - Africa
    - Set of 12 pages of printed pictures of African missionary work scenes published by the Religious Tract Society, no date (Box OV8, Folder 9)
    - African poster of natives greeting a boat full of missionaries, no date (Box OV8, Folder 10)
    - Set of 63 colored African posters for teaching the Bible with a corresponding Guide Book, 2005 (Box OV8, Folder 11)
    - Set of six colored African missionary posters done in a cartoon style, no date (Box OVd-1 #14, Folder 1)
  - China
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Many of these posters have been digitized and described as part of the Chinese Christian Posters project at Boston University. See http://ccposters.com/library/yale-divinity-library/.
    - 2 long banners with scripture texts John 5: 28-29 and Mark 8:36, no date (Box OV9, Folder 1)
    - Set of 8 posters on cardboard with depictions of the story of the Prodigal Son and Chinese text, no date (Box OV9, Folder 2)
    - 2 colored posters with images and symbols on them, including large red crosses, no date (Box OV9, Folder 3)
    - Set of 20 colored Chinese posters with images on one side and symbols on the other., no date (Box OV9, Folder 4)
    - Set of 8 colored Chinese posters with images and symbols., no date (Box OV9, Folder 5)
    - Long poster with a series of images depicting the story of the Prodigal Son, no date (Box OV9, Folder 6)